When night falls, the wolves will hunt.
Wolves at the Door is a horror, thriller film directed by John R. Leonetti.
Four friends gather at an elegant home during the Summer of Love, 1969.
Unbeknownst to them, deadly visitors are waiting outside.
What begins as a simple farewell party turns to a night of primal terror as the intruders stalk and
torment the four, who struggle for their lives against what appears to be a senseless attack.
Sharon, played by Katie Cassidy.
Abigail, played by Elizabeth Henstridge.
Wojciech, played by Adam Campbell.
Jay, played by Miles Fisher.
John, played by Chris Mulkey.
Mary, played by Jane Kaczmarek.
Wolves at the Door is a 2016 American horror film directed by John R.
Leonetti and written by Gary Dauberman.
The film is loosely based on the murder of Sharon Tate, the pregnant wife of Roman Polanski, and her friends in 1969 by members of the
Manson Family, and, though not considered an installment in the franchise, takes place within The Conjuring Universe.
The cast features Katie Cassidy, Elizabeth Henstridge, Adam Campbell and Miles Fisher as four friends who are stalked and murdered by a group
of intruders at a farewell party, with Eric Ladin reprising his role as Detective Clarkin from Leonetti's 2014 film Annabelle.
The film, produced by New Line Cinema and The Safran
Company and distributed by Warner Bros.
Pictures, was first theatrically released in India on October 21, 2016, followed by
Germany on March 2, 2017, and in the United Kingdom on March 17, 2017.
It was released on Digital HD in the United States on April 18, 2017.
It was panned by critics, garnering a rare 0%
approval rating on Rotten Tomatoes.
The film was mainly criticized for its depiction of the Tate murders
and was described as "exploitative" and "misconceived."
The film explores themes of california, based on true
story, attack, home invasion, summer of love.
The tone is dark and intense.